[{"answer": "Be quiet, man, I got neighbor", "docId": "Pineapple-Express.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": " Somebody killed somebody?!", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": " Somebody killed somebody?!", "docId": "Pineapple-Express.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Somebody killed a cop, a lady and a guy", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Yeah, man! I can't believe it. A cop! A lady, and a guy", "docId": "Pineapple-Express.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "No! A guy", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Somebody killed a cop, a lady and a guy", "docId": "Pineapple-Express.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "A cop killed a guy", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "No! I panicked. I was having a coughing fit, I crashed, I crashed into a car. Fuck, two cars. They must've heard at least. They knew someone was there", "docId": "Pineapple-Express.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "No. I don't think so. No", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I'm not calling the cops", "docId": "Pineapple-Express.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Yeah. I saw some blood", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "So, you are actually the only guy in town with this weed", "docId": "Pineapple-Express.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "And am I the only guy you gave it to", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "No! We're not going anywhere", "docId": "Pineapple-Express.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "There's nothing out there, that's why we're here. God, man, you scared the fucking shit out of me", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": " This can't be right", "docId": "Pineapple-Express.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "It says, uh..", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "We should beat it out of his sellout brains. You're a shitty friend, Red! Fuck the Casino! Go alone", "docId": "Pineapple-Express.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "He knows my name too", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "  Shit. They're actually here to kill him", "docId": "Pineapple-Express.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " I don't know", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "ARGGG!!", "docId": "Pineapple-Express.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "No! I'm my friend's dealer, I'm ", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Shut up dad", "docId": "Pineapple-Express.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "What are you going to do? What should we do", "qsentId": 26}]